(Leonard:)Just not against their will.
(Leonard:)You really think you should be
eating that cake?
(Sheldon:)Why?
(Leonard:)If you're gonna be
(Leonard:)a trophy husband
for a rich wife,
(Leonard:)you might want
to watch your waistline.
(Raj:)He's right.
(Raj:)A minute on the lips,
a lifetime on the hips.
(Howard:)Yeah, ha-ha.
(Howard:)First of all, I'm not threatened
by my fiancée's success.
(Howard:)I'm proud of her.
(Howard:)And secondly,
I have my own career.
(Leonard:)Until you have kids.
(Sheldon:)Good news, Raj.
(Sheldon:)I got the blood work
back from the lab.
(Sheldon:)You're okay to stay for a while.
(Raj:)When did you take my blood?
(Sheldon:)Not important.
(Sheldon:)Your sugar was a little high.
(Sheldon:)I'd follow up
with your regular physician.
(Sheldon:)In the meantime, I have some
paperwork here
(Sheldon:)for you to go over.
(Raj:)What the hell is this?
(Sheldon:)Boilerplate stuff.
(Sheldon:)A modified roommate agreement
for a temporary house guest.
(Sheldon:)And a living will and durable
power of attorney.